<Threads xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="BoardContent.xsd">
  <Thread>
    <title>Stop me if you've heard this one...</title>
    <date>12/02/2019</date>
    <OriginalPost>
      <sent>0</sent>
      <poster>BlindRiver44</poster>
      <content>Ok, I know this recipe is getting shared a lot, but a sizeable enough portion of the community seems to be getting results. The recipe goes:<![CDATA[<br><br>]]>One demiard of Himalayan Rock Salt<![CDATA[<br>]]>One sprig of herbs<![CDATA[<br>]]>One vial of essential oils<![CDATA[<br>]]>and One catalyst (Feel free to get creative with this part)<![CDATA[<br><br>]]>I'm still setting up my sanctuary, so I'm hoping the more experienced practitioners on this board can try it out. Please comment below with your results, and those of you without a working setup like me, please share to support the community!</content>
    </OriginalPost>
    <Comments>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>I'm not telling you again, quit reposting this boiler-plate garbage and get OFF my board.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>BlindRiver44</poster>
        <content>Like I have to listen to you, this is a service to the community, it doesn't even violate any of the guidlines.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>Sure, we haven't seen a public post about it yet... But everyone's seen this in their private servers a million times. It's basically copypasta at this point.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>1</sent>
        <poster>Godslayer04</poster>
        <content>kek. Trying to keep information out of the hands of the proletariat, Meta? This is a new low even for you~</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>Not validating this with a response. Please review the FAQs before posting again Godslayer.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>1</sent>
        <poster>Godslayer04</poster>
        <content>Still always gotta have the last laugh, I see!</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>another_Lilim</poster>
        <content>this whole comment thread is off-topic and should be removed...</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>anonymous</poster>
        <content>yea, this is why everyone but shitposters like OP and oldfags have moved on . . .</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>BlindRiver44</poster>
        <content>going to work. If I get back and nobody's said anything relevant I'll take this down myself.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>JustRantaroKun</poster>
        <content>more low quality bait.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>1</sent>
        <poster>Godslayer04</poster>
        <content>I'll try it @OP. Just got my streaming rig set up yesterday; i'll buy this stuff today and stream the ritual tomorrow.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>Strike 2. Self promotion.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>anonymous</poster>
        <content>Hate the mods as much as the next guy, but can we seriously get these kids off here? This is serious occultic inquiry, not social media.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>SaltyBlood</poster>
        <content>site's dead. catch me on the board this originated from: http://occult.info/dolpyne/post?1306080435525435393</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>Banned.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>anonymous</poster>
        <content>rip.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>REMINDER THAT PROMOTING OTHER BOARDS IS A BANNABLE OFFENSE.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>another_Lilim</poster>
        <content>looking forward to the stream Godslayer...</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>JustRantaroKun</poster>
        <content>salty may be stupid, but he was still one of the good ones. </content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>_Serafim_</poster>
        <content>We should hold a memorial in my Disquiet server. Rest In Peace SaltyBlood. May your everlasting soul find solitude in death.</content>
      </Post>
    </Comments>
  </Thread>
</Threads>