<Threads xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="BoardContent.xsd">
  <Thread>
    <title>Son of man...</title>
    <date>NULL</date>
    <OriginalPost>
      <sent>0</sent>
      <poster>INVALID USER ID</poster>
      <content><![CDATA[it goes,<br>something,<br>like this]]></content>
    </OriginalPost>
    <Comments>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>I'm not telling you again, quit reposting this boiler-plate garbage and get OFF my board.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>FlopSux</poster>
        <content>How's this troll keep getting on here anyway? Should the server even be processing posts without a date?</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>He's probably some pathetic hacker who thinks he's hot stuff.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>Well guess what, "INVALID USER ID", I'm tracking your IP you neanderthal. My Vassals we be there any second to eradicate your worthless troll existence.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>1</sent>
        <poster>Godslayer04</poster>
        <content>lol, maybe OP's not so bad after all. think i'll stream this recipe and use it to take the mods down a notch.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>Self promoting again, are we Godslayer04? You should be grateful we even TOLERATE that kind of narcisistic drivel on this board.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>I can't wait for your stream where you FOOLISHLY glorify this TROLL ACCOUNT and expose yourself for the worthless faker we ALL know you REALLY are.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>1</sent>
        <poster>Godslayer04</poster>
        <content>bad look always posting twice in a row like that. i imagine you just slamming enter incoherently while sperging out</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>YOU'RE LUCKY TO BE ON A BOARD THAT STILL TOLERATES THAT KIND OF LANGUAGE!</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>If I weren't so DEDICATED to your FREEDOM OF SPEECH I'd have BANNED you already.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>1</sent>
        <poster>Godslayer04</poster>
        <content>lol, stream's up guys: witch.tv/Godslayer04</content>
      </Post>
    </Comments>
  </Thread>
</Threads>