<Threads xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="BoardContent.xsd">
  <Thread>
    <title>A Voice...</title>
    <date>12/03/2019</date>
    <OriginalPost>
      <sent>1</sent>
      <poster>GodSlayer04</poster>
      <content>Those of you who saw my stream just earlier today witnessed what may have been the first proven, documented contact with an other-wordly entity in the history of this or any species. I highly encourage those moved by my actions to follow this account, and pledge your tithes to my dark procession via Paytreon. However, what followed the events of that stream, from my subjective viewpoint, was truly extraordinary. A voice came to me. I will not attempt to recall nor decipher it's exact message, HOWEVER, I can say with certainty that someone or something contacted my inner thoughts. This being taunted me for attempting to seek the truth, and challenged me to face it with my power as a summoner.<![CDATA[<br><br>]]>Discuss.</content>
    </OriginalPost>
    <Comments>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>You're dangerously nearing self-promotion again GodSlayer04.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>JustRantaroKun</poster>
        <content>lol. maybe "the voice of god" over here is starting to get to you, lmao.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>another_Lilim</poster>
        <content>i've been hearing voices in my head too lately... i wonder if that means i'm also becoming more powerful...</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>anonymous</poster>
        <content>Just because a few people liked your stream, doesn't mean you can post bullshit like this with no evidence and expect us to theorize. I see right through you.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>_Seraphim_</poster>
        <content>GodSlayer, my child, we are all happy to see you getting off to a good start with your livestreams, but please, do not disrespect the work of those that came before you. You are not the first and will not be the last, I assure you.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>kuromachina</poster>
        <content>no way. seraph. just watch the stream.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>anonymous</poster>
        <content>it was something else alright, but can you really call that solid evidence? could be some live2d shit...</content>
      </Post>
    </Comments>
  </Thread>
  <Thread>
    <title>Signs of paranormal activity..?</title>
    <date>12/03/2019</date>
    <OriginalPost>
      <sent>0</sent>
      <poster>kuromachina</poster>
      <content>something in the forest. seems alive. would investigate but very busy.</content>
    </OriginalPost>
    <Comments>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>This doesn't violate the guidelines, however, I think that only serves to show how much further this site had ought to go in enforcing quality standards. ONCE AGAIN, I stress this. Please. Check the FAQs for the style guide and proper posting etiquette.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>1</sent>
        <poster>GodSlayer04</poster>
        <content>The thing with kuro though, is you always know he means it. I'll be sure to investigate.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>kuromachina</poster>
        <content>thanks GS. rooting for you since the stream.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>1</sent>
        <poster>GodSlayer04</poster>
        <content>I appreciate your support, in whatever way you choose to show it!</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>JustRantaroKun</poster>
        <content>sucks seeing a founding member of this board shill for some kid.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>_Seraphim_</poster>
        <content>Rantaro, your manner is crude, but your heart is pure. Heaven mourns he who dubs himself "too busy" to stay informed.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>Let's please try to stay on the topic of this post, however shallow its contents. We would do well to not let the events of one stream drown out other voices.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>1</sent>
        <poster>GodSlayer04</poster>
        <content>Says the so-called "voice of god", eh?</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Xx_MetatronsBlade_xX</poster>
        <content>The voice of God is my master, I am merely its arm.</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>Red Reign</poster>
        <content>Ok, um, hi, I know I'm new here, but like, can you seriously not give any more detail than that?</content>
      </Post>
      <Post>
        <sent>0</sent>
        <poster>kuromachina</poster>
        <content>yes. stay away. this is the real deal.</content>
      </Post>
    </Comments>
  </Thread>
</Threads>
